For him?
Yes, go, he is late.
Sorry beta, so
Rigu, so much cash in your bag?
Where did you get all this cash from?
You did steal, right? Tell me the truth.
Ma'am, this is my pocket money savings.
Actually my daily pocket money is
₹10,000.  And this is just my seven days
pocket money savings.
Yes ma'am, Triun is a big
businessman uptown.  He is very rich.  Ray.
Good.  Ok son, sorry.  Sorry sorry.
Brother Triguna, what does your father do
that you are so rich?
Hey friend, we have a lot of work to do.
Import, export, finance,
advertising companies and investment in share market.
One second, Papa's calling.
[Music]
Yes dad.
One second.  Shahrukh Khan, Salman Khan.
Salman Khan.   Yes
dad.  Salman Khan done.  Ok.
What is the money for, brother?
Hey, it's our company, so dad is getting
a product of our company shot.
Ad shoot.  So you are asking whether it should be done by Shahrukh
or Salman?  Salman is fine, right?
Brother, please get our photo taken with Salman.
Hey friend, I will tell you.  Yes, I will get it done.   Let's
go.